alright guys welcome back and in this video I'm going to talk to you about a
好的伙伴欢迎 回来 视频我要 和你谈谈
dictionary in Python now whenever you have a dictionary in real life you have
无论何时你在Python中的字典 你有 现实生活中的字典
a bunch of words and they're associated with a bunch of definitions now in Python we have names for these instead
一堆词，他们是相关的 现在有一堆定义 Python 我们有这些名称
of words and definitions we call them keys and values and the cool thing about
我们称之为单词和定义 键和值以及有关很酷的事情
Python is you're not only limited to you know like a definition like you would
Python不仅 限于 你 知道像你一样的定义
think in a dictionary you can also use numbers and stuff like that so let me
想在字典中你也可以使用 数字和 类似的 东西 让我
show you an example right now so the first thing you have to do is of course
现在给你看一个例子吧 你要做 的第一件事 当然 是
just name it whatever you want and then set it equal to and then use those curly
只要你想要的任何名称，然后 设置它等于然后使用那些卷曲
braces now inside your curly braces you're going to have sets of a key and a
现在你的花括号里面有括号 你会有一套 钥匙和一套钥匙
value and you can have as many as you want you can have one you can have 100
价值， 你可以拥有尽可能多的人 希望 你 能拥有100个
it doesn't matter so for the key I'll just write Tony and for the value
对于钥匙我没关系 只写托尼和价值
actually let me use single quotes so write the key and think of this like the
实际上让我使用单引号 写下关键并想到 这一点
word in the dictionary and then add a colon and then after that colon is the
字典中的单词然后添加一个 结肠然后结肠就是了
value and I'll write cool smells so say that this dictionary is um storing like
价值，我会写出很酷的气味所以说 这本字典就像存储一样
everyone in my class so again the key which is Tony and the value of this is
我 班上的每个人都是如此的关键 这是托尼和这个值 是
cool but smells so whenever you want to add a new item what you have to do is
很酷，但每当你 想要的 时候都会闻到 添加一个新项目你需要做的是
just separate them with commas and then I'm too lazy to do the format again so I'm just going to do that alright so
然后 用逗号分隔它们 我太懒了 再这样 做 格式 了 我只是要做到这一点 好吗 这样
this key can be for Emma and her value can be I don't know I'll say she sits
这个 关键可以 用于艾玛和她的价值 我 可以不知道我会说她坐着
behind me let's add one more so comma umm one more person could be like Lucy
在我身后， 让我们再添加一个逗号 嗯，还有一个人可能像露西
and her value will be I don't like Lizzie because she asks too many
她的价值将是我不喜欢的 丽齐，因为她问了太多
questions alright so now we have a dictionary called classmates and it's
问题好吧现在我们 有了 字典叫同学，就是这样
made up of three key value pairs Toni Emma and Lucy so I guess I can go ahead
由三个关键价值对Toni组成 艾玛和露西，所以我想我可以继续
and just print this out real quick so if you just print
然后快速打印出来，如果 你打印
the name of your dictionary without specifying any one of these individually
你 没有 的字典名称 单独指定其中任何一个
then there's just going to go ahead and print the whole thing as expected now
那么只是 要继续 前进， 现在按预期印刷整个东西
obviously you can do cooler things in this you can print something like um
显然你可以做更酷的事情 你可以打印像嗯这样的东西
classmates and then in square brackets put the key Emma so this is pretty much
同学然后在方括号内 把钥匙放在艾玛身上 就是这样
saying print the value of Emma and of course Emma's value is sits behind me so
说打印艾玛的价值 和 当然，艾玛的价值就在我身后
again you can do this with each individual item in your dictionary or
再次， 你可以 做到这一点 您字典中的单个项目或
I'll show you guys something really cool this is probably the coolest thing that
我会告诉你们一些非常 酷的 东西 这可能是最酷的事情
you can do with it what you can do is instead of having to go through your
你可以做的就是你可以 做的 而 不必经过你
dictionary one at a time like Emma Tony okay who's the next Lucy o mg that's
字典在一个像艾玛托尼时间 好吧，谁是下一个 Lucy o mg那个
taken forever there's a real quick way that you can loop through it so what you
永远采取 这是一个真正的快速方式 你可以循环通过它，所以 你
do is you use a for loop and then you know how we just gave our for loop a
你做的是使用for循环 吗？ 知道我们如何给我们的for循环了
variable name and that was the name of whatever item
变量的名称，这是名 什么项目
it was looping through at the time well since a dictionary is composed of keys
它在当时很好地循环 因为字典是由键组成的
in values we actually need to give it two variables so we'll say K and V and this is what people typically use and
在价值观中，我们实际上需要给予它 两个变量，所以我们会说K和V和 这是人们通常使用的东西
this is pretty much saying whenever we loop through it treat K is the key so
无论什么时候我都会这么说 循环通过它对待K是关键 所以
the first time is going to be Tony then Emma the Lucy and V is going to be the value so this is going to be cool but
在第一时间将是托尼 然后 艾玛的露西和V将成为 价值所以这会很酷但是
smell sits behind me and ask too many questions and then after this we just
气味坐在我身后，问太多了 问题然后我们就这样
need to say in classmates items simple enough so again this is the dictionary
需要 在同学的项目中说简单 够 了，这就是字典
that's looping through and it's going to loop through all of the items so now I
这是循环的，它会 发生 循环遍历所有 项目所以现在我
can just put something like print arm kay I don't know let me think of
可以放一些 像打印臂的 东西 凯我不知道让我想到 的
something stupid okay I don't even know how I can have this
一些 愚蠢的好吧 我甚至不知道怎么能有 这个
make sense okay I just do something really easy k plus V which is pretty
有道理好吧， 我只是做一些事情 真的很 容易k + V 很漂亮
much going to print out this and this simple enough
很多东西打印出这个和 这个 很简单
so actually let me get rid of these so it doesn't confuse you so as you can see
所以实际上让我摆脱这些 你 可以 看到它并不会让你感到困惑
since we didn't have spaces let me add spaces real quick so our bunch together
因为我们没有空格让我加 空间真快，所以我们 在一起
what it does is you build a dictionary right here your dictionary o is composed
它的作用是你 建立 一本字典 就在这里你的词典 是由 你 组成的
of keys in values we have three of them in this case and what this loop did is it loop through this dictionary and for
值中的键我们 有 三个 在这种情况下，什么这个循环所做 的是 它循环通过这个词典 并为
each item in your dictionary it printed the key and the value so of course the key is just the name
您 打印 的 词典中的每个项目 关键和价值 所以当然关键 只是名字
and the value is a little note we wrote about them so that is what this little
这个价值 是我们写的一点点 关于他们这就是 这个 小小的东西
program does and that is how you can build a dictionary in Python and in the
程序确实如此，你就是这样 在Python和中创建一个字典
next couple tutorials they're actually going to be a lot more interesting than
接下来几个教程他们实际上 会变得更有趣
this because I'm going to start showing you guys how to work with modules and
这是因为我要开始展示 你们这些如何使用模块和
also how to build a very simple web crawler it's probably going to be the
还有如何建立一个非常简单的网站 履带吊它可能会 成为
coolest program roommate we made up to date so think guys for watching and I'll
最酷的节目室友我们做了 约会，所以想伙计们观看，我会
see you next time
下次见